(This drama is related to specific characters, institutions, and groups It has nothing to do with the case and is purely fictitious (I hereby inform you)
(Ang dramang ito ay nauugnay sa mga partikular na tauhan, institusyon, at grupo Wala itong kinalaman sa kaso at ito ay gawa-gawa lamang (ipinapaalam ko sa iyo)
(Seasoning, sesame oil, chili powder)
(Seasoning, sesame oil, chili powder)
I need someone to follow a guy.
I need someone to follow a guy.
who do you want to follow
who do you want to follow
Although Douxue will take action against gangsters
Bagama't kikilos si Douxue laban sa mga gangster
But he won't bully innocent people
Pero hindi niya binubully ang mga inosenteng tao
His name is…
His name is…
Li Douxue
Li Douxue
Usually stalking someone…
Usually stalking someone…
All for some purpose
All for some purpose
If you tell me your purpose first
If you tell me your purpose first
things might go more smoothly
things might go more smoothly
(Episode 7) You said you have the right to stay in Mingdangdong Dogeng
(Episode 7) Sabi mo may karapatan kang manatili sa Mingdangdong Dogeng
Are there 100 places?
Are there 100 places?
It's true
totoo naman
I heard that the occupancy rights are 20 square meters.
Narinig ko na 20 square meters ang occupancy rights.
Previously it cost less than 3 million won can buy it
Previously it cost less than 3 million won can buy it
Now it has risen to 40 to 50 million won.
Now it has risen to 40 to 50 million won.
Oh my god
Diyos ko
first time i saw A place where the price is so ridiculously high
first time i saw Isang lugar kung saan napakataas ng presyo
What right of occupancy?
What right of occupancy?
This is not an ordinary apartment building right of occupancy
Ito ay hindi isang ordinaryong apartment building right of occupancy
It is the right to occupy the apartment released during the city update.
Karapatan na sakupin ang apartment na inilabas sa panahon ng pag-update ng lungsod.
I heard the competition is very fierce
I heard the competition is very fierce
Whether it is Cheong Wa Dae or relevant government departments, Those guys from the city government
Cheong Wa Dae man ito o mga kaugnay na departamento ng gobyerno, Yung mga taga city government
All before the news comes out
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Just mobilize all your relatives I'm snapping up the land over there.
Kinukuha ko ang lupa doon.
So how is the intelligence possible? Has it reached us?
Kaya paano posible ang katalinuhan? Nakarating na ba sa atin?
It's just like war
Parang digmaan lang
Take good care and don't let the deadbeat come back.
Mag-ingat at huwag hayaang bumalik ang deadbeat.
It must never happen again The bloody conflict just now
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know. Ang madugong labanan ngayon lang
Yes eldest brother
Oo panganay na kapatid
I'll come to hand over my shift tomorrow
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Thank you for your hard work
Salamat sa iyong pagsusumikap
Got it, brat
Nakuha ko, brat
Thank you for taking charge of this big case.
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Take one portion and treat the brothers to barbecue
Kumuha ng isang bahagi at ituring ang mga kapatid sa barbecue
Just use the other one where needed.
Gamitin lang ang isa kung kinakailangan.
Hey what are you looking at
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Brother, these are really just enough to buy barbecue.
Kuya, sapat lang talaga itong pambili ng barbecue.
The brothers were injured and paid for medical expenses
Ang mga kapatid ay nasugatan at binayaran para sa mga gastusin sa pagpapagamot
It costs a lot of money…
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Boy, I'm serious
Boy, seryoso ako
Am I going to give you your hard-earned money? Do you swallow it yourself?
Ikaw ba mismo ang lumulunok nito?
Everything must be accumulated slowly
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
It's time for me to go
Kailangan kong pumunta ngayon
The brothers’ medical expenses alone cost two hundred.
Dalawang daan ang gastos ng magkapatid sa pagpapagamot.
Damn you guy, this is too much.
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Go to the baseball stadium and sell tickets to scalpers. I make about the same amount of money as this
Pumunta sa baseball stadium at magbenta ng mga tiket sa mga scalper. Kumikita ako ng halos kaparehong halaga ng pera nito
Bro, give these to the brothers.
Bro, ibigay mo ito sa mga kapatid.
I know
nakikita ko
What about us?
Paano naman tayo?
Don’t we get a monthly salary?
Hindi ba tayo nakakakuha ng buwanang suweldo?
But…
pero…
Yeah, forget it if I can't subsidize it.
Oo, kalimutan mo ito kung hindi ko ito ma-subsidize.
At least we can't drain our brothers dry.
Hindi bababa sa hindi namin matuyo ang aming mga kapatid.
Brother, I brought people here
Kuya, nagdala ako ng mga tao dito
let her in
papasukin mo siya
welcome you
maligayang pagdating sa iyo
(Lee Yunae)
(Lee Yunae)
We suddenly came to you. Did it scare you?
Bigla kaming lumapit sayo. Tinakot ka ba nito?
Brother, did he tell you to remit money?
Kuya, sinabi ba niyang mag-remit ka ng pera?
How much does he want you to wire?
Magkano ang gusto niyang i-wire mo?
If the boss knew I told him...
Kung alam ng boss na sinabi ko sa kanya...
I will really die miserably
Mamamatay talaga ako ng kawawa
Don't worry, we will keep it secret
Huwag mag-alala, sikreto namin ito
How much does he want you to wire?
Magkano ang gusto niyang i-wire mo?
50 million won
50 milyong won
Fifty million won?
Limampung milyong won?
Brother Guangzhuo really called you Do you want to remit 50 million won?
Tinawag ka talaga ni Kuya Guangzhuo Gusto mo bang mag-remit ng 50 million won?
Yes it's true
Oo totoo
Five checks for 10 million won in total
Limang tseke para sa 10 milyong won sa kabuuan
He also said that a man should be loyal
Dapat din daw maging loyal ang lalaki
I heard him fart
Narinig ko siyang umutot
Really…
Talagang…
Fifty million won…
Limampung milyong won…
Brothers are very unhappy
Lubhang malungkot ang magkapatid
Now there is a valid reason
Ngayon ay may wastong dahilan
The time has come, right?
Dumating na ang oras, tama ba?
Just now
Ngayon lang
Douxue, let’s get rid of Guangzhuo.
Douxue, tanggalin na natin ang Guangzhuo.
I can be the first one
Maaari akong maging una
The time has indeed come
Dumating na talaga ang panahon
Brother Guangzhuo was not like that before...
Hindi naman ganoon si Brother Guangzhuo noon...
It's not all because of damn greed
Hindi lahat dahil sa kasakiman
Douxue also said
Sabi din ni Douxue
He will divide us when there is only petty profit
Hahatiin niya tayo kapag maliit lang ang tubo
But when there is gold and silver, he will definitely keep it to himself
Ngunit kapag may ginto at pilak, tiyak na itatago niya ito sa kanyang sarili
So…
Kaya…
Are you about to take action?
Malapit ka na bang kumilos?
No
Hindi
Why not?
Bakit hindi?
Because I have the final say
Dahil ako ang may huling say
Hello Douxue
Hello Douxue
Douxue
Douxue
Big brother…
Kuya…
(Diagnosis Choi Young-sik) non-obstructive azoospermia
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
The date of diagnosis was three months before the wedding
Ang petsa ng diagnosis ay tatlong buwan bago ang kasal
sorry
maawa ka
If only I had known earlier
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
I'm really sorry
Sorry talaga
Almost...
halos...
(Violent clashes occurred at the Mingdangdong demolition site)
(Naganap ang marahas na sagupaan sa lugar ng demolisyon ng Mingdangdong)
There's something I'm curious about
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
You haven't seen Huang Cichang for a long time, right?
Matagal mo nang hindi nakikita si Huang Cichang, di ba?
Right
oo
Chief Huang, isn't he coming now?
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
It seems so
Parang ganun
That is to say
Ibig sabihin
Are we It’s time to find another place to party.
tayo ba Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
See you next time Luo
See you next time Luo
No need
Hindi na kailangan
Do you want to drink?
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
People think we eat delicacies from mountains and seas every day
Iniisip ng mga tao na kumakain tayo ng mga delicacy mula sa mga bundok at dagat araw-araw
As the saying goes, all it takes is one missed meal
Gaya nga ng kasabihan, ang kailangan lang ay isang hindi nakuhang pagkain
No matter how much you eat, you can't make up for it.
Kahit gaano karami ang kainin mo, hindi ka makakabawi.
So please eat on time
Kaya please kumain sa oras
Ruzhen, please help me cook.
Ruzhen, tulungan mo akong magluto.
It's not too late to start now
Hindi pa huli ang lahat para magsimula ngayon
Is that why you came to us so late?
Kaya ba late ka pumunta sa amin?
What else should I do?
Ano pa ba ang dapat kong gawin?
My mother even called me and asked me to spend the night outside.
Tinawagan pa ako ng nanay ko at pinapalipas ako ng gabi sa labas.
I don’t know any relatives in Seoul
Wala akong kakilala sa Seoul
You want me, a weak woman, to stay in a hotel Very scary
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know. Sobrang nakakatakot
Yes, it's a good bet you came to us
Oo, magandang pustahan na pumunta ka sa amin
It seems she has a man
Mukhang may lalaki siya
That must be it
Ganun dapat
Otherwise, why would I suddenly kick you out?
Kung hindi, bakit bigla kitang ipagtabuyan?
What do you mean by that?
Ano ang ibig mong sabihin diyan?
What's wrong?
anong mali?
Anyway, her husband is gone. What does it matter?
Anyway, wala na ang asawa niya. Ano ang mahalaga?
Do you want to be like the women of the Joseon Dynasty? Be a widow until death?
Gusto mo bang maging katulad ng mga kababaihan ng Joseon Dynasty? Maging balo hanggang kamatayan?
I will go to Zhenyu's room to sleep
Pupunta ako sa kwarto ni Zhenyu para matulog
You guys should go to sleep too
Tulog na rin kayo
That room is very cold
Napakalamig ng kwartong iyon
She actually has a man
May lalaki talaga siya
What's going on?
Anong nangyayari?
Oh my god, I'm so shy...
Diyos ko, nahihiya ako...
OMG…
OMG…
So shy
Sobrang nahihiya
These are the pajamas Tetsuo wore before I don't know if it looks good on you.
Ito ang mga pajama na suot ni Tetsuo noon Hindi ko alam kung mukhang maganda ito sa iyo.
If you tell me beforehand I can buy your pajamas first
Kung sasabihin mo sa akin ng maaga Bibili muna ako ng pajama mo
Good night then
Magandang gabi kung gayon
You know it will fit you even without wearing it.
Alam mo babagay sayo kahit hindi mo suot.
After all, it's my son's pajamas
Tutal, pajama ito ng anak ko
Brother Loyalty
Kapatid na Katapatan
live with me
tumira sa akin
Three meals a day with you
Tatlong pagkain sa isang araw kasama ka
Now I don’t want to miss it anymore
Ngayon ay ayaw ko nang palampasin ito
What you have suffered over the years
Kung ano ang iyong dinanas sa paglipas ng mga taon
I will make it up to you
Babayaran kita
Brother Loyalty, I am satisfied now.
Kuya Loyalty, kontento na ako.
Brother Zhongzhong, thank you
Kapatid na Zhongzhong, salamat
I will find a chance to tell Tetsuo
Hahanap ako ng pagkakataon para sabihin kay Tetsuo
Tell him about our relationship
Sabihin sa kanya ang tungkol sa aming relasyon
You see what I mean?
Nakikita mo ang ibig kong sabihin?
I know you said it many times
I know you said it many times
if someone asks me
if someone asks me
I would say the lady's son I delivered the baby myself
I would say the lady's son I delivered the baby myself
Don't worry
Huwag kang mag-alala
(Diagnosis Choi Young-sik) Is it non-obstructive azoospermia?
(Diagnosis Choi Young-sik) Is it non-obstructive azoospermia?
(Dean Luo Yaoquan) Dean, please
(Dean Luo Yaoquan) Dean, please
Because of the child’s father’s political leanings
Dahil sa political leaning ng ama ng bata
may affect His appointment as prosecutor
maaaring makaapekto His appointment as prosecutor
(Dean Luo Yaoquan)
(Dean Luo Yaoquan)
Dean, please help me
Dean, please help me
I only have that son left now
I only have that son left now
If something goes wrong with him
If something goes wrong with him
I…
ako…
I won't survive, Dean.
I won't survive, Dean.
please help me
please help me
I will never forget this kindness
Hinding hindi ko makakalimutan ang kabaitang ito
Keiko, you're back
Keiko, you're back
Yes
Oo
How are you doing these days?
Kumusta ka ngayong mga araw?
Keiko, sorry
Keiko, sorry
can you go out for a moment
can you go out for a moment
OK
OK
so
kaya
How do you answer
How do you answer
I was so scared that I couldn't speak
I was so scared that I couldn't speak
It was too late, but it was so fast that my husband happened to show up.
Huli na, ngunit napakabilis na nagkataong nagpakita ang aking asawa.
Just say that Tetsuo is your biological son.
Just say that Tetsuo is your biological son.
I've heard that if you want to serve in an important organization
Narinig ko na kung gusto mong maglingkod sa isang mahalagang organisasyon
A wealth survey will be conducted
A wealth survey will be conducted
But the other person always makes me feel a little unusual
Ngunit ang ibang tao ay palaging nagpaparamdam sa akin na medyo kakaiba
We are not in our hometown anymore He also came here
We are not in our hometown anymore He also came here
And…
At…
What's wrong?
anong mali?
That person looks familiar
That person looks familiar
When living in Lishui
When living in Lishui
I have followed guests from Mrs. Chu's house before Passed by several times
Nakasunod na ako sa mga bisita mula sa bahay ni Mrs. Chu Passed by several times
That person looked very similar to the guest at that time
Kamukhang-kamukha ang taong iyon sa panauhin noong panahong iyon
How is it possible
Paano ito posible
You must have read it wrong
You must have read it wrong
I feel like that person seems to know something Just came to the door
I feel like that person seems to know something Just came to the door
It made me break out in a cold sweat
It made me break out in a cold sweat
How is it possible
Paano ito posible
Is there something he should know?
Is there something he should know?
what
ano
Please completely forget the wrong ideas in your mind
Mangyaring ganap na kalimutan ang mga maling ideya sa iyong isipan
Tetsuo is my son
Tetsuo is my son
Got it?
Naintindihan mo?
I also hope to forget
I also hope to forget
But it's not something I can control
But it's not something I can control
you really are...
ikaw talaga...
sorry
sorry
I will talk to her well when I go back
I will talk to her well when I go back
Let's go first
mauna na tayo
Get up quickly
Bumangon ka dali
please wait a moment
mangyaring maghintay ng ilang sandali
A studious mother
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
what
Ano
Our family has caused a lot of trouble for you before.
Ang aming pamilya ay nagdulot ng maraming problema para sa iyo noon.
If you come to help, you can also supplement the family income.
Kung pupunta ka para tumulong, maaari mo ring dagdagan ang kita ng pamilya.
I remember you were good at driving a cultivator, right?
Naalala ko magaling ka magdrive ng cultivator diba?
Life is really full of surprises
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
I'm already this age He actually asked me to take a driver's license test
Pinapa-test niya talaga ako sa driver's license
It's so ridiculous
Sobrang katawa-tawa
Don't dwell on it, just help.
Wag mo nang isipin, tulungan mo lang.
No matter how I think about it, I feel She was afraid that I would reveal Tetsuo's life experience.
Kahit anong isipin ko, nararamdaman ko Natatakot siya na ibunyag ko ang karanasan ni Tetsuo sa buhay.
She just wants me to stay by her side to monitor me
Gusto niya lang na manatili ako sa tabi niya para subaybayan ako
Why can’t you let go of Tetsuo now?
Bakit hindi mo kayang bitawan si Tetsuo ngayon?
How could I forget him
Paano ko siya makakalimutan
If there was an eraser in the world that could erase memories Please bring it to me
Kung may pambura sa mundo na kayang burahin ang mga alaala Mangyaring dalhin ito sa akin
You are really...
Ikaw talaga...
So you don't help me
Error 504 (Server Error)!!1504.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Of course I want to help
Syempre gusto kong tumulong
This way you can see it often My son who became a prosecutor
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
I know... I just won't say it...
Alam ko... hindi ko lang sasabihin...
Really
talaga
What's so hard about driving?
Ano ang mahirap sa pagmamaneho?
(Prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong)
(Prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong)
Come and see the urban renewal areas
Halina at tingnan ang mga urban renewal areas
Now these three places are left
Ngayon ang tatlong lugar na ito ay naiwan
I think it would be best if everyone can buy it
Sa tingin ko, mas mabuti kung lahat ay makakabili nito
If you have to choose
Kung kailangan mong pumili
Just buy it here...
Bumili ka na lang dito...
(Boss of Star Industrial, Byun Hak-soo)
(Boss ng Star Industrial, Byun Hak-soo)
next time work
sa susunod na trabaho
Just like this Jisoo you...
Ganito ka lang Jisoo...
(Violent clashes occurred at the Mingdangdong demolition site Mobilization of gangsters leads to violent clashes)
(Naganap ang marahas na sagupaan sa demolition site ng Mingdangdong Ang pagpapakilos ng mga gangster ay humantong sa marahas na sagupaan)
(Gangster mobilization leads to violent clashes Violent suppression of residents at Mingdangdong demolition site)
(Ang pagpapakilos ng gangster ay humahantong sa marahas na pag-aaway Marahas na panunupil sa mga residente sa Mingdangdong demolition site)
Choi Cheol-woong, congratulations on your appointment as prosecutor.
Choi Cheol-woong, binabati kita sa iyong appointment bilang prosecutor.
I originally planned to keep my distance from you.
Plano ko noong una na panatilihin ang aking distansya mula sa iyo.
But you are now a prosecutor
Pero prosecutor ka na ngayon
If I didn't come to say congratulations You will definitely be angry with me forever
Kung hindi ako dumating para bumati Siguradong magagalit ka sa akin ng tuluyan
That's why I made up my mind to come see you
Kaya naman nagdesisyon akong puntahan ka
That's right
tama yan
I was planning to do it if you didn't show up
I was planning to do it kung hindi ka sumipot
I'm going to sue you
Idedemanda kita
Shero
Shero
I heard a lawyer I know say
narinig kong sabi ng isang kakilala kong abogado
I was fined just for parking illegally on the red line. It would be difficult to become a prosecutor
Pinagmulta ako para lang sa ilegal na pagparada sa pulang linya. Mahirap maging prosecutor
So honestly I thought you had no chance
Sa totoo lang I thought you had no chance
You are truly amazing…
Kahanga-hanga ka talaga…
If you miss it because of the fine It's a pity that I'm such a talented person.
If you miss it because of the fine It's a pity that I'm such a talented person.
The senior management of our unit is very discerning, right?
Very discerning ang senior management ng unit namin, di ba?
Can boast enough
Can boast enough
You are a disease
You are a disease
Do you and Brother Douxue meet often?
Do you and Brother Douxue meet often?
That silly boy
That silly boy
I moved again a while ago
I moved again a while ago
i'm looking for him
i'm looking for him
He will come later
He will come later
I called him
tawag ko sa kanya
Really?
talaga?
You are very clever at times like this
You are very clever at times like this
Does he know I'm here too?
Does he know I'm here too?
I told him
sabi ko sa kanya
Will he do it because I'm here? If you want to hide from me, you won’t come.
Will he do it because I'm here? If you want to hide from me, you won’t come.
He will definitely come
He will definitely come
He is better than anyone They all still want me to become a prosecutor.
He is better than anyone They all still want me to become a prosecutor.
And I have something important to tell him.
And I have something important to tell him.
What's going on
Anong nangyayari
Promise me first that you won't be angry
Promise me first that you won't be angry
OK I'm not angry
OK I'm not angry
what's going on
anong nangyayari
The prosecutor who came in at the same time as me Sitting in the box next to
Yung prosecutor na kasabay ko pumasok Sitting in the box next to
Because we received a report
Because we received a report
(Violent clashes occurred at the Mingdangdong demolition site)
(Naganap ang marahas na sagupaan sa lugar ng demolisyon ng Mingdangdong)
Violent conflict in Mingdangdong Doggeng
Marahas na tunggalian sa Mingdangdong Doggeng
The identities of the participants are still being investigated.
Iniimbestigahan pa ang pagkakakilanlan ng mga kalahok.
But I was also shocked when I saw these photos
Pero laking gulat ko rin nang makita ko ang mga litratong ito
"Should I say something to him?"
"May sasabihin ba ako sa kanya?"
"When I'm indecisive"
"Kapag hindi ako makapagdesisyon"
(live acoustic guitar singing) "He left"
(live acoustic guitar singing) "Umalis siya"
"I gave my heart" Hello Prosecutor Choi, congratulations.
"Binigay ko ang puso ko" Hello Prosecutor Choi, congratulations.
"I shed tears for him"
"Napaluha ako para sa kanya"
How are you doing lately?
Kamusta ka lately?
"I will also dream..." You stinky gangster
"Managinip din ako..." Mabaho kang gangster
You moved behind my back Is this just for doing this?
Lumipat ka sa likod ko Ito ba ay para lamang sa paggawa nito?
Is that you in the photo?
Ikaw ba yung nasa litrato?
Yes
Oo
Where did these photos come from?
Saan nagmula ang mga larawang ito?
Sent by people
Ipinadala ng mga tao
This is what the underworld does
Ito ang ginagawa ng underworld
If you want to teach me a lesson, just leave.
Kung gusto mo akong turuan ng leksyon, umalis ka na lang.
Hello Cui Zhexiong
Kumusta Cui Zhexiong
Why don't we just arrest him and imprison him?
Bakit hindi na lang natin siya arestuhin at ikulong?
Why are you showing me these photos?
Bakit mo ipinapakita sa akin ang mga larawang ito?
You really haven't changed at all...
Wala ka talagang pinagbago...
Tetsuo, use your clever head Use it in the right place
Tetsuo, gamitin mo ang iyong matalinong ulo Use it in the right place
Dingchen…
Dingchen…
Wait a minute...
Sandali...
Every time the three of us meet It doesn't end well
Sa tuwing magkikita kaming tatlo Hindi maganda ang pagtatapos nito
Please don’t take photos like this again.
Mangyaring huwag kumuha ng mga larawang tulad nito muli.
That's why I asked you to be a prosecutor
Kaya naman hiniling kong maging prosecutor ka
what do you want me to do
anong gusto mong gawin ko
If you get information like this Just help me, right?
Kung makakuha ka ng impormasyong tulad nito Tulungan mo na lang ako ha?
Do you ask the prosecutor to protect gangsters?
Hinihiling mo ba sa tagausig na protektahan ang mga gangster?
have you forgotten
nakalimutan mo na ba
I know I still owe you
Alam kong may utang pa ako sayo
But it shouldn’t be repaid in this way, right?
Ngunit hindi ito dapat bayaran sa ganitong paraan, tama ba?
No matter if I'm a gangster or not
Hindi mahalaga kung ako ay isang gangster o hindi
It doesn’t matter if you are a prosecutor or not.
Hindi mahalaga kung ikaw ay isang tagausig o hindi.
You have to repay the debt you owe me Until I yell stop
Kailangan mong bayaran ang utang mo sa akin Hanggang sa huminto ako sa pagsigaw
I get it…
Naiintindihan ko…
But don’t involve Dingchen
Pero huwag mong idamay si Dingchen
Don't let her become unhappy because of you
Huwag mong hayaan na maging malungkot siya dahil sayo
I never involved her
I never involved her
That's why I moved
Kaya naman lumipat ako
Also
Gayundin
Same for you
Pareho para sa iyo
I know you are afraid that Dingchen will be taken away by me
Alam kong natatakot ka na maagaw ko si Dingchen
why
bakit
Because you are a sore loser
Dahil ikaw ay isang masakit na talunan
But you figure it out
Pero intindihin mo
This is not love, but possessiveness
Ito ay hindi pag-ibig, ngunit pagiging possessive
Brat
Brat
Coming...
Darating...
Brother, who is coming?
Kuya, sino ang darating?
Don't know
hindi ko alam
Brother, please come in
Brother, please come in
Thank you for your hard work, Boss Lian.
Thank you for your hard work, Boss Lian.
thank you
salamat po
As long as you can do your part for the country
As long as you can do your part for the country
We are always ready to be dispatched
We are always ready to be dispatched
Hello…
Hello…
Say hello
Say hello
This is Team Leader Wu, our minister’s confidant.
Ito si Team Leader Wu, ang pinagkakatiwalaan ng ating ministro.
He is the person with real power in our unit
He is the person with real power in our unit
You know what I mean
You know what I mean
Team leader Wu said he wants to see you So we came together
Team leader Wu said he wants to see you So we came together
My name is Lian Guangzhuo. Please give me some advice.
My name is Lian Guangzhuo. Mangyaring bigyan ako ng ilang payo.
My surname is Wu
My surname is Wu
This is the case The brother in charge of on-site command
This is the case The brother in charge of on-site command
He and I are like sworn brothers in Taoyuan Guan Yu and Zhang Fei
He and I are like sworn brothers in Taoyuan Guan Yu and Zhang Fei
We are brothers
We are brothers
Come and say hello
Come and say hello
My name is Li Douxue
Ang pangalan ko ay Li Douxue
Have we met before?
Nagkita na ba tayo dati?
Thank you for your hard work
Salamat sa iyong pagsusumikap
Although there was a bit of bloodshed
Although there was a bit of bloodshed
But you handled things well
But you handled things well
thank you for your compliment
salamat sa iyong papuri
Boss Lian, come here
Boss Lian, come here
yes
oo
It is said that apartment buildings will be built in more areas in the future.
Sinasabing ang mga gusali ng apartment ay itatayo sa mas maraming lugar sa hinaharap.
Yes
Oo
I'll contract out the window frames for the apartment to you.
Kukunin ko sa iyo ang mga frame ng bintana para sa apartment.
what
ano
Won't you give me the right to move in?
Won't you give me the right to move in?
Right of occupancy?
Right of occupancy?
Are you still not satisfied with this?
Are you still not satisfied with this?
don't you know How much can you earn from window frames alone?
hindi mo ba alam How much can you earn from window frames alone?
That's not what I meant
Hindi iyon ang ibig kong sabihin
Section Chief Thank you
Section Chief Thank you
Why are you still dumbfounded? Let the lady come in quickly.
Why are you still dumbfounded? Let the lady come in quickly.
Section Chief
Section Chief
I found one for you A special lady comes in
I found one for you A special lady comes in
Really?
talaga?
I'm looking forward to it
Inaasahan ko ito
Stay tuned
Stay tuned
Yeon Joo
Yeon Joo
boss
boss
Just promise me once Wait a minute...
Just promise me once Sandali...
This is my first time asking you to do this
This is my first time asking you to do this
I don't want
ayoko
Yeonjoo, I'm sorry
Yeonjoo, I'm sorry
I really don't want to go in
I really don't want to go in
Yeon Joo, please save me just once.
Yeon Joo, please save me just once.
ok
ok
Boss, please let me go
Boss, please let me go
Don't you know very well that I hate this kind of thing the most?
Hindi mo ba alam na pinakaayaw ko ang ganitong bagay?
Of course I know...
Of course I know...
So just once is enough
Kaya isang beses lang sapat na
Yanzhu, please let me ask you for help
Yanzhu, hayaan mo akong humingi ng tulong sa iyo
Today’s guest is a high-ranking guest
Ang panauhin ngayon ay isang matataas na panauhin
Go get acquainted It will also be very helpful to you
Magpakilala ka Malaki rin ang maitutulong nito sa iyo
That's what you insist on I won’t be an actor anymore
Yan ang pinagpipilitan mo Hindi na ako magiging artista
Hello…
Hello…
Hey, I've been begging you so hard
Hoy, nakikiusap ako sayo
Do you really want to do this to me? Are you sure?
Gusto mo ba talagang gawin ito sa akin? Sigurado ka ba?
Boss, I just want to ask you not to do this to me.
Boss gusto ko lang hilingin na wag mong gawin sakin to.
You really want to drink wine as a penalty instead of eating the toast...
Gusto mo talagang uminom ng alak bilang parusa sa halip na kainin ang toast...
what is this doing
anong ginagawa nito
What are you doing?
anong ginagawa mo
Why don't you let go?
Bakit ayaw mong bitawan?
Wait a minute, it hurts...
Sandali, masakit...
You little bastard, let go now
Ikaw munting bastard, bitawan mo na
This woman is really...
Ang babaeng ito talaga...
my neck… Hello
leeg ko… Hello
Be more respectful
Maging mas magalang
ok sorry
ok sorry
Hello…
Hello…
I'm here to meet your boss
Nandito ako para makipagkita sa boss mo
Then please go in alone. She even said she didn't want to go in.
Then please pumasok ka mag-isa. Sinabi pa niyang ayaw niyang pumasok.
what
ano
Let's go
Tara na
Hello Song Yanzhu...
Hello Song Yanzhu...
stop
huminto
Wait a minute...
Sandali...
Why is it so noisy?
Bakit ang ingay nito?
It hurts...
Masakit...
Boss Yin, what are you doing before you come in?
Boss Yin, ano ang ginagawa mo bago ka pumasok?
Where is Song Yeon-joo?
Nasaan si Song Yeon-joo?
I want to ask you
gusto kitang tanungin
This guy is the one who twisted my wrist
Itong lalaking ito ang pumulupot sa pulso ko
Let Song Yanzhu run away
Hayaang tumakas si Song Yanzhu
Abominable
Kasuklam-suklam
what
ano
Brother, sorry
Kuya, sorry
Because Song Yanzhu doesn’t want to go in But he dragged her here
Dahil ayaw pumasok ni Song Yanzhu Pero hinila niya siya dito
Brat...
Brat...
Don't you know how important this is?
Hindi mo ba alam kung gaano ito kahalaga?
Who are you? How dare you decide her stay or go without permission?
sino ka ba How dare you decide her stay or go without permission?
Brother, be gentle with your feet.
Kapatid, maging banayad sa iyong mga paa.
how are you
kumusta ka
Won't you get out of the way?
Hindi ka ba aalis sa daan?
Big brother
Kuya
Impolite brat
Impolite brat
Is this how you manage your younger brother?
Ganito ba ang pamamahala mo sa iyong nakababatang kapatid?
Catch Song Yanzhu quickly
Mahuli si Song Yanzhu nang mabilis
Go and get it back...
Pumunta at ibalik ito ...
Big brother
Kuya
It's my fault. Hit me.
Kasalanan ko to. Saktan mo ako.
What are you guys like?
Ano ba kayo?
Hello Li Douxue
Kamusta Li Douxue
Now you teach him a lesson in front of me
Ngayon tinuturuan mo siya ng leksyon sa harap ko
Brat, hurry up
Brat, hurry up
Good job
Magandang trabaho
are you kidding
nagbibiro ka ba
This is a lesson, you brat.
This is a lesson, you brat.
Get up...
Get up...
Hurry up and teach him a lesson
Hurry up and teach him a lesson
You boy
Ikaw boy
What do you want now?
Ano ang gusto mo ngayon?
Brat
Brat
enough
sapat na
Yeon Joo
Yeon Joo
Boss Yin, bring her in quickly
Boss Yin, bring her in quickly
I'll settle the score with you later
I'll settle the score with you later
Do you know?
alam mo ba
Boss Yin, hurry up
Boss Yin, hurry up
Yanzhu, come here quickly...
Yanzhu, come here quickly...
Hello, I am movie star Song Yeon-joo.
Hello, I am movie star Song Yeon-joo.
I love watching your movies
I love watching your movies
I have read almost all of your works
I have read almost all of your works
Of course, while my wife is away
Of course, while my wife is away
Sirs, please take a look
Sirs, please take a look
She is both beautiful and good at acting
She is both beautiful and good at acting
It's just impeccable.
It's just impeccable.
Thanks for the compliment
Thanks for the compliment
Let's listen to Miss Song Yeon-joo sing a song
Let's listen to Miss Song Yeon-joo sing a song
Come on, everyone applaud
Halika, palakpakan ang lahat
Thank you for your compliments
Thank you for your compliments
But I'm not going to sing
But I'm not going to sing
I’m not going to pour wine for you either.
I’m not going to pour wine for you either.
Song Yanzhu, what’s wrong with you?
Song Yanzhu, what’s wrong with you?
I plan not to be Song Yeon-joo anymore
I plan not to be Song Yeon-joo anymore
What you like Is it the movie star Song Yeon-joo?
Kung ano ang gusto mo Is it the movie star Song Yeon-joo?
My real name is Park Jung Mi
My real name is Park Jung Mi
from this moment on
mula sa sandaling ito
I'm not a movie actor, and I'm not Song Yeon-joo either.
Hindi ako artista sa pelikula, at hindi rin ako si Song Yeon-joo.
I want to live as Park Jung Mi
I want to live as Park Jung Mi
Then I can go now
Then I can go now
-what is she talking about -What's going on?
-what is she talking about -Anong nangyayari?
What are you doing?
anong ginagawa mo
Sorry, I took her away first.
Sorry, I took her away first.
Sorry, what should I do now?
Sorry, what should I do now?
Would you like a glass of soju with the omelette?
Gusto mo ba ng isang baso ng soju na may omelette?
Your tone of voice is too indifferent, right?
Your tone of voice is too indifferent, right?
Don't look at me like this. I have a baby face.
Don't look at me like this. I have a baby face.
I don't drink with actors
I don't drink with actors
I just decided not to do it
I just decided not to do it
I don't drink with my sister
I don't drink with my sister
Egg hot compress is not effective for bruises
Egg hot compress is not effective for bruises
Apply this
Apply this
Apply ice once or twice and it won't hurt anymore
Maglagay ng yelo isang beses o dalawang beses at hindi na ito masakit
If the bruise spreads, apply warm compresses with a towel
Kung kumalat ang pasa, lagyan ng mainit na compress gamit ang tuwalya
It will get better soon
It will get better soon
Are you a gangster too? You know so much
Are you a gangster too? Ang dami mong alam
I do know a lot
I do know a lot
The little bastard can at least fight back.
The little bastard can at least fight back.
But in this circle you can only get beaten
But in this circle you can only get beaten
If you go to the hospital, the news will spread
If you go to the hospital, the news will spread
Over time I became an expert on bruises
Over time I became an expert on bruises
If you're curious about other types of wounds Just ask me how to deal with it
If you're curious about other types of wounds Just ask me how to deal with it
What if you were hit with a stick and broke a bone?
Paano kung natamaan ka ng patpat at nabali ang buto?
What's wrong
anong mali
Don’t you know this?
Hindi mo ba alam ito?
Of course you have to go to the hospital, idiot
Of course you have to go to the hospital, idiot
You are simply a psychopath
You are simply a psychopath
really sorry
sorry talaga
please forgive me
patawarin mo sana ako
It doesn’t matter…
It doesn’t matter…
I didn't come here to drink in the first place.
I didn't come here to drink in the first place.
I came here because I have something to discuss with Boss Lian.
Pumunta ako dito dahil may pag-uusapan ako kay Boss Lian.
So you don’t have to pay too much attention
So you don’t have to pay too much attention
Is there anything I can do to help?
May maitutulong ba ako?
I will definitely try my best to help
I will definitely try my best to help
Only gives you the exclusive right to sell the window frame
Binibigyan ka lang ng eksklusibong karapatang ibenta ang window frame
You must be dissatisfied
You must be dissatisfied
How is it possible
Paano ito posible
Don’t just be responsible for driving away the demolition households
Huwag lamang maging responsable sa pagtataboy sa mga demolisyon na kabahayan
How about participating directly in the program?
How about participating directly in the program?
What? Directly involved?
ano? Directly involved?
Of course I want to
Of course I want to
But we haven’t been able to raise that much money yet.
Ngunit hindi pa kami nakakaipon ng ganoong kalaking pera.
Boss Lian only needs to prepare 20% of the funds.
20% lang ng pondo ang kailangan ni Boss Lian.
We can prepare the rest
We can prepare the rest
We will also personally allocate the land to be developed
Personal din nating ilalaan ang lupang bubuuin
100% certain
100% certain
This is not just in Seoul
This is not just in Seoul
It is a metropolitan plan that covers the entire metropolitan area.
Ito ay isang metropolitan plan na sumasaklaw sa buong metropolitan area.
Of course the profits are astronomical
Of course the profits are astronomical
But I have a condition
Pero may kondisyon ako
You say it
sabihin mo na
first
una
We hold 70% of the shares and you hold 30%
We hold 70% of the shares and you hold 30%
We will give you 10% more shares
We will give you 10% more shares
because of money laundering and tax expenses
because of money laundering and tax expenses
All included in Boss Lian’s shares
All included in Boss Lian’s shares
Got it
Nakuha ko
Second, even in front of King Yama
Second, even in front of King Yama
I can't even tell you about our cooperative relationship.
Hindi ko man lang masabi sa inyo ang tungkol sa cooperative relationship namin.
If this is violated
If this is violated
The consequences may be disastrous
The consequences may be disastrous
I swear
I swear
I will definitely be loyal to you
I will definitely be loyal to you
And…
At…
I have one more thing to ask you
I have one more thing to ask you
Please tell me
Pakisabi sa akin
Please walk slowly
Mangyaring maglakad nang dahan-dahan
Please walk carefully and slowly
Mangyaring maglakad nang maingat at dahan-dahan
Douxue
Douxue
Did I go a little too far just now?
Did I go a little too far just now?
It's okay, brother
It's okay, brother
But why does he come to you?
But why does he come to you?
nothing
wala
He just came to please me
He just came to please me
Continue to help him like you are doing now
Continue to help him like you are doing now
Really
talaga
So boring
So boring
That's right
tama yan
I would have done it even if he didn't say it
Gagawin ko sana kahit hindi niya sabihin
Hello Douxue
Hello Douxue
Don't be angry
Huwag kang magalit
After all I am the boss
Tutal ako naman ang boss
But he was embarrassed in front of the guests
Pero napahiya siya sa harap ng mga bisita
I'm too excited
Masyado akong excited
Right
Tama
This…
Ito…
You take it and treat your little brothers to delicious food.
Kunin mo ito at ipapakain ang iyong mga maliliit na kapatid sa masarap na pagkain.
relax
magpahinga
Thank you bro
Salamat kuya
No. Let’s get off work.
Hindi. Alis na tayo sa trabaho.
Please walk slowly, brother
Magdahan-dahan ka kuya
So crowded
Sobrang sikip
where
saan
here
dito
These funds alone are absolutely not enough
Ang mga pondong ito lamang ay ganap na hindi sapat
No matter how hard I think, I can't think of a way
Kahit anong hirap ang iniisip ko, wala akong maisip na paraan
drink
inumin
Cow, you can eat it from head to tail
Baka, maaari mong kainin ito mula ulo hanggang buntot
Not even willing to throw away the internal organs A nation that cooks and eats
Hindi man lang handang itapon ang mga laman-loob Isang bansang nagluluto at kumakain
It's probably just us
Malamang tayo lang
We often come here to eat the offal soup
Madalas kaming pumupunta dito para kumain ng offal soup
Yes
Oo
The eldest brother also said that we should be together for the rest of our lives. Brothers who show their sincerity to each other
Sinabi rin ng panganay na kapatid na dapat ay magkasama kami habang buhay. Mga kapatid na nagpapakita ng kanilang sinseridad sa isa't isa
Yes
Oo
That's why I came to see you again
Kaya naman naparito ulit ako para makita ka
Do you remember what I said?
Naalala mo ba yung sinabi ko?
The person who will inherit my country from now on
Ang taong magmamana ng aking bansa mula ngayon
This is not Li Douxue who became a monk halfway.
Hindi ito si Li Douxue na naging monghe sa kalagitnaan.
It’s you who worked hard with me when I was young
Ikaw ang nagsumikap sa akin noong bata pa ako
you know tiger
alam mo tigre
Will push his child off the cliff
Itutulak ang kanyang anak sa bangin
Then only raise children who can crawl back.
Pagkatapos ay palakihin lamang ang mga bata na maaaring gumapang pabalik.
you are like that
ganyan ka
And that guy Douxue
At ang lalaking si Douxue
It has nothing to do with eating offal soup with me.
Wala itong kinalaman sa pagkain ng offal na sopas kasama ko.
Come
Halika
Thank you for your hard work
Salamat sa iyong pagsusumikap
We hold 70% of the shares and you hold 30%
Hawak namin ang 70% ng mga pagbabahagi at hawak mo ang 30%
We will give you 10% more shares
Bibigyan ka namin ng 10% pang shares
because of money laundering and tax expenses
dahil sa money laundering at mga gastos sa buwis
All included in Boss Lian’s shares
Lahat kasama sa shares ni Boss Lian
I know
alam ko
Second, even in front of King Yama
Pangalawa, kahit sa harap ni Haring Yama
I can't even tell you about our cooperative relationship.
Hindi ko man lang masabi sa inyo ang tungkol sa cooperative relationship namin.
If this is violated
Kung ito ay nilabag
The consequences may be disastrous
Ang mga kahihinatnan ay maaaring nakapipinsala
Because we need to know what big brother is doing
Dahil kailangan nating malaman kung ano ang ginagawa ni kuya
If there is a 30% stake in the development company
Kung may 30% stake sa development company
How much money can you make
Gaano karaming pera ang maaari mong kumita
Although only 30%
Bagama't 30% lamang
But development projects cost several billions Billions of dollars
Ngunit ang mga proyekto sa pagpapaunlad ay nagkakahalaga ng ilang bilyon Bilyong dolyar
Of course the income is at the level of a large company
Syempre nasa level ng malaking kumpanya ang kita
We…
Kami…
Eat this business
Kainin ang negosyong ito
This is a chance for brother
Ito na ang pagkakataon para kay kuya
They will get rid of big brother Leave the work to us?
Tatanggalin nila si kuya Ipaubaya sa amin ang trabaho?
That's right
tama yan
It doesn't matter to them who they do it for
Hindi mahalaga sa kanila kung para saan nila ito ginagawa
What matters is how good that person is
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Are you saying this is the level of a big company?
Sinasabi mo bang ito ang antas ng isang malaking kumpanya?
Let's just vote
Vote na lang tayo
Get out of this miserable situation
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
You should have guessed the other party’s identity, right?
Dapat nahulaan mo ang pagkakakilanlan ng kabilang partido, tama ba?
So what?
Kaya ano?
You should consider carefully
Dapat mong pag-isipang mabuti
Those people live in a different world than us
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
They can…
Maaari silang…
Kill someone?
pumatay ng tao?
Kill us?
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
South Korea's CIA
CIA ng South Korea
I'm so scared
Takot na takot ako
You can quit if you're scared
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Do you want to grab it?
Gusto mo bang sunggaban?
what
Ano
how do you know
paano mo nalaman
sorry
sorry
Because money is tight recently So I sold it temporarily
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know. Kaya ibinenta ko ito pansamantala
I know you don't like it
Alam kong hindi mo ito gusto
I can stop doing it now...
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
If you want to make a name for yourself all over the country Even more so
Kung gusto mong gumawa ng pangalan para sa iyong sarili sa buong bansa
Selling drugs doesn't matter Just wait until you gain some weight and then stop selling it.
Maghintay lamang hanggang sa tumaba ka at pagkatapos ay ihinto ang pagbebenta nito.
Isn't it?
hindi ba?
Brother, why did you suddenly say that?
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
Yongbi
Yongbi
Big brother
Kuya
But suddenly it expanded
Error 500 (Server Error)!!1500.That’s an error.There was an error. Please try again later.That’s all we know.
You give it a try
Subukan mo ito
And I can't get involved in drugs. in related cases
And I can't get involved in drugs. in related cases
You understand
Naiintindihan mo
I will keep it in mind, brother
I will keep it in mind, brother
No
Hindi
why
bakit
Why do you always say no?
Why do you always say no?
If you say no, can't we do it?
If you say no, can't we do it?
Well, I can't
Well, I can't
Am I your dog...
Am I your dog...
Because I'm the boss
Because I'm the boss
Team Leader Wu, only we can know about this.
Team Leader Wu, only we can know about this.
Don’t let anyone else in the company know
Don’t let anyone else in the company know
Yes
Oo
But how much do you know
But how much do you know
I only know the minister and the chief of security
Ministro at chief of security lang ang kilala ko
Don't fund them with company funds
Don't fund them with company funds
Help them get a bank loan
Help them get a bank loan
Can't leave them with us Transaction records
Can't leave them with us Transaction records
Got it
Nakuha ko
Also
Gayundin
In addition, we retain 10% of our equity
In addition, we retain 10% of our equity
I can't guarantee I'll still be sitting How long have you been in this position?
I can't guarantee I'll still be sitting How long have you been in this position?
It’s time for Team Leader Wu to prepare to retire.
Oras na para sa Team Leader Wu na maghanda para magretiro.
Isn't it?
hindi ba?
thank you
salamat po
Who told you to lie down
Who told you to lie down
Lie down for me
Humiga ka para sa akin
Douxue, wait a minute
Douxue, wait a minute
Who allows you to call the boss by his name?
Who allows you to call the boss by his name?
Operation Captain
Operation Captain
Lie down
humiga ka
Douxue, okay, stop fighting.
Douxue, okay, stop fighting.
Hello
Hello
If you dare to steal money again
If you dare to steal money again
I will definitely beat you to death next time
I will definitely beat you to death next time
Let's go, brother
Let's go, brother
are you okay
okay ka lang ba
Let me go, brat
Let me go, brat
Abominable
Kasuklam-suklam
1 million won
1 milyon won
You just stole 1 million won Was he beaten like this?
You just stole 1 million won Was he beaten like this?
And that money is not what I want to use
And that money is not what I want to use
I'm buying suits for the new boys.
I'm buying suits for the new boys.
Just took that money
Just took that money
In addition to paying rent and eating
In addition to paying rent and eating
He doesn't let us spend money at all
He doesn't let us spend money at all
Big brother learns from Li Dou
Big brother learns from Li Dou
Really stingy
Really stingy
you
ikaw
Have you really never received any pocket money?
Have you really never received any pocket money?
Yes, brother
Yes, brother
I live with the money from my family
I live with the money from my family
Brother, I'm still borrowing money from my friends.
Kuya, nanghihiram pa ako ng pera sa mga kaibigan ko.
Did they keep the money for themselves?
Did they keep the money for themselves?
Otherwise, how could I...
Otherwise, how could I...
How could I want to steal money?
How could I want to steal money?
That guy spoke very nicely Say we are a family
That guy spoke very nicely Say we are a family
Hey, can this be called a family?
Hey, can this be called a family?
He doesn't think we are family
He doesn't think we are family
Yongbi
Yongbi
You take me in
You take me in
I will help you take revenge
I will help you take revenge
You and Dou Xue have been inseparable since we were in prison.
Ikaw at si Dou Xue ay hindi mapaghihiwalay mula noong tayo ay nasa bilangguan.
How do you want me to believe you?
Paano mo ako gustong maniwala sayo?
I learn from Dou
I learn from Dou
I took all the money from the office safe
I took all the money from the office safe
30 million won
30 million won
I could have taken the money and run away
I could have taken the money and run away
But I came to you
But I came to you
Because I want revenge
Because I want revenge
I seem to be able to feel your sincerity
I seem to be able to feel your sincerity
These are just the tip of the iceberg
These are just the tip of the iceberg
In Lian Guangzhuo's vault
In Lian Guangzhuo's vault
There is ten times more money than this
There is ten times more money than this
I run errands for him every month So I know it very well
I run errands for him every month So I know it very well
Doesn’t Lian Guangzhuo dislike going to the bank?
Hindi ba ayaw ni Lian Guangzhuo na pumunta sa bangko?
indeed
talaga naman
Now working in the underworld
Now working in the underworld
money is power
money is power
Just steal Lian Guangzhuo's treasury
Just steal Lian Guangzhuo's treasury
Each of my brothers can save a few million more
Each of my brothers can save a few million more
Lian Guangzhuo and Li Douxue
Lian Guangzhuo and Li Douxue
Let's get rid of them all in one go.
Let's get rid of them all in one go.
I want that too
I want that too
But the timing doesn't seem right
But the timing doesn't seem right
Hello
Hello
What are you arguing about?
What are you arguing about?
what are you going to do
ano ang gagawin mo
Don't move at all
Huwag kang gumalaw
I am prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong
I am prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong
You are Yongpil
You are Yongpil
nice to meet you
Ikinagagalak kitang makilala
Actually
Sa totoo lang
My target is not you, it’s Lian Guangzhuo
My target is not you, it’s Lian Guangzhuo
You know Lian Guangzhuo
You know Lian Guangzhuo
kick you out
kick you out
Take Li Douxue with you
Take Li Douxue with you
Trying to find ways to strengthen his power everywhere
Sinusubukang maghanap ng mga paraan upang palakasin ang kanyang kapangyarihan sa lahat ng dako
Selling alcohol in a bar and laundering money is the most basic thing
Ang pagbebenta ng alak sa isang bar at paglalaba ng pera ang pinakapangunahing bagay
He also helped the company suppress the labor union.
Tinulungan din niya ang kumpanya na sugpuin ang unyon ng manggagawa.
even use violence Force residents in Tugeng area to leave
even use violence Force residents in Tugeng area to leave
It's really a headache
It's really a headache
But they don’t know what backing they have
But they don’t know what backing they have
It runs away as fast as a loach and is hard to catch
Tumatakbo ito na kasing bilis ng loach at mahirap hulihin
now because of them
now because of them
The public opinion situation is very bad
The public opinion situation is very bad
The government says it wants to protect citizens
The government says it wants to protect citizens
So…
Kaya…
We have to catch someone to scare the monkeys
We have to catch someone to scare the monkeys
to calm public opinion
to calm public opinion
It has been decided from above
It has been decided from above
you can take over the organization
you can take over the organization
Then learn from Lian Guangzhuo and Li Dou Give us the criminal evidence
Then learn from Lian Guangzhuo and Li Dou Give us the criminal evidence
Then we can quell the dissatisfaction of the people practice patriotism
Pagkatapos ay maaari nating sugpuin ang kawalang-kasiyahan ng mga tao isagawa ang pagkamakabayan
You can also take revenge He can also take over the organization smoothly
You can also take revenge He can also take over the organization smoothly
Kill two birds with one stone, kill two birds with one stone Isn’t it the best of both worlds?
Patayin ang dalawang ibon gamit ang isang bato, patayin ang dalawang ibon gamit ang isang bato Isn’t it the best of both worlds?
How is it
Paano ba naman
Do you think I will believe you?
Do you think I will believe you?
Yongbi
Yongbi
What are we doing catching a little fish like you?
Ano ang ginagawa namin nanghuhuli ng munting isda na katulad mo?
Our goal is to catch big fish
Our goal is to catch big fish
Even if your name is reported to the newspaper, no one will recognize it.
Kahit na iulat ang iyong pangalan sa pahayagan, walang makakakilala nito.
At least like Lian Guangzhuo To be discernible
At least like Lian Guangzhuo Upang makilala
Don't look down on people
Don't look down on people
No one knows what will happen in the future.
No one knows what will happen in the future.
Yes
Oo
So
Kaya
Yongbi
Yongbi
in this world
sa mundong ito
Day and night coexist
Magkasama ang araw at gabi
Can there be only flowers and plants in this world?
Maaari bang may mga bulaklak at halaman lamang sa mundong ito?
Have rabbits that eat grass
Have rabbits that eat grass
There must also be wild wolves and tigers that eat rabbits
Dapat mayroong mga ligaw na lobo at tigre na kumakain ng mga kuneho
The organization always needs someone to accept it
Ang organisasyon ay palaging nangangailangan ng isang tao upang tanggapin ito
Just accept it
Tanggapin mo na lang
However
Gayunpaman
Don't get into big trouble and cooperate with us well
Huwag makisali sa malaking gulo at makipagtulungan sa amin ng mabuti
OK
OK
Hey, drive faster
Hey, drive faster
is…
is…
Did you know that during the Imjin Japanese Rebellion?
Alam mo ba iyon noong panahon ng Imjin Japanese Rebellion?
General Yi Sun-shin refused to listen to Seonjo's words No troops were sent
Tumanggi si Heneral Yi Sun-shin na makinig sa mga salita ni Seonjo No troops were sent
Later I got slapped The story of joining the army in white clothes
Later I got slapped The story of joining the army in white clothes
People who originally disobeyed the king’s orders It must be executed immediately
Mga taong orihinal na sumuway sa utos ng hari It must be executed immediately
But General Yi Sun-shin because of his great achievements
Ngunit si Heneral Yi Sun-shin dahil sa kanyang mga dakilang tagumpay
Seonjo gave him a gold medal to avoid death
Seonjo gave him a gold medal to avoid death
No matter what you do wrong
No matter what you do wrong
He can avoid death once
He can avoid death once
A token like that
A token like that
This is the death-free gold medal
This is the death-free gold medal
This document is really hard to get
This document is really hard to get
Don't go around showing off to others
Don't go around showing off to others
OK, then I'll stamp it...
OK, then I'll stamp it...
No, I'll finish pressing the fingerprint first
No, I'll finish pressing the fingerprint first
If you press your fingerprint again, this document will be Save your life
Kung pinindot mo muli ang iyong fingerprint, ang dokumentong ito ay magiging Save your life
Everything is done
Lahat ay tapos na
(Certificate from the Supreme Prosecutor’s Office)
(Sertipiko mula sa Supreme Prosecutor's Office)
You are here
Nandito ka
Sorry I'm late
Sorry I'm late
It's okay. Please sit down.
ayos lang. Mangyaring maupo.
Do you want to order a drink first?
Do you want to order a drink first?
It's okay, no need
It's okay, no need
good
mabuti
Thank you for thinking of me so much
Thank you for thinking of me so much
But I'm retired
But I'm retired
when
kailan
yesterday
kahapon
So please find another actor
So please find another actor
This movie will definitely be a hit
This movie will definitely be a hit
This role is also suitable for you
This role is also suitable for you
And we will definitely give you dividends
And we will definitely give you dividends
If…
If…
An actress who fell in love with a gangster
An actress who fell in love with a gangster
Doesn't it matter?
Doesn't it matter?
Not in a movie, but in real life
Not in a movie, but in real life
I'm such a madman
I'm such a madman
Do you remember the last time you came to the filming set? Pick up my gangster
Naaalala mo ba ang huling beses na pumunta ka sa set ng paggawa ng pelikula? Pick up my gangster
Yes
Oo
i like him very much
i like him very much
I want to date him
Gusto ko siyang ligawan
am i crazy
am i crazy
Thank you for coming to your appointment today
Thank you for coming to your appointment today
Then I'll leave first
Then I'll leave first
But you are really crazy
But you are really crazy
Be careful not to choke. Eat slowly.
Be careful not to choke. Eat slowly.
I have to finish eating quickly
I have to finish eating quickly
Go back to work on the case
Go back to work on the case
Don't you have something important to tell me?
Don't you have something important to tell me?
do you have a girlfriend
may girlfriend ka ba
I heard other prosecutors
I heard other prosecutors
When I was in training school, I would be chased by girls.
Noong nasa training school ako, hahabulin ako ng mga babae.
Did you call me back out of curiosity?
Did you call me back out of curiosity?
How
Paano
Are you worried that your son won't get a wife?
Are you worried that your son won't get a wife?
not like that
hindi ganun
that's why
kaya lang
If you want to get married
If you want to get married
There will be one less officiant
There will be one less officiant
Forget it
Kalimutan mo na
Let’s talk about it later
Pag-usapan natin ito mamaya
do you want coffee
gusto mo ba ng kape
Mom, you have a boyfriend
Mom, you have a boyfriend
No
Hindi
I was right, right?
I was right, right?
Actually…
Sa totoo lang…
That's great. That's great.
Ang galing. Ang galing.
do you really think so
do you really think so
Of course
Syempre
My mother is so young and beautiful
My mother is so young and beautiful
I have to stay alone in an empty house for the rest of my life Is this true?
Kailangan kong manatili mag-isa sa isang bakanteng bahay sa buong buhay ko totoo ba ito?
I originally thought that if you didn't have a boyfriend
Akala ko dati kung wala kang boyfriend
I want to introduce you to someone
I want to introduce you to someone
so good
napakabuti
Tetsuo
Tetsuo
Why, are you worried that I will object?
Why, are you worried that I will object?
Is it because of dad?
Is it because of dad?
Didn’t dad have…
Didn’t dad have…
Will my son help him pass on the incense of the Cui family?
Tutulungan ba siya ng aking anak na magpasa ng insenso ng pamilya Cui?
However
Gayunpaman
what does that person do
what does that person do
where did you meet How did we know each other?
where did you meet How did we know each other?
he is a good man
he is a good man
I'll arrange to meet you later
I'll arrange to meet you later
Really exciting
Really exciting
My mother actually started falling in love
My mother actually started falling in love
You are much better than me
You are much better than me
very cold
napakalamig
You go in quickly
You go in quickly
You go back I'm leaving
Bumalik ka aalis na ako
(Terrible outsider team)
(Terrible outsider team)
The cheers from the audience came from the baseball stadium
Nagmula sa baseball stadium ang tagay ng mga manonood
Hello Dingchen
Hello Dingchen
If you convince Director Lee Chang-ho
If you convince Director Lee Chang-ho
You must let me sing a movie soundtrack
You must let me sing a movie soundtrack
If you don't let me sing
If you don't let me sing
I'll pack my bags and go back to Lishui
I'll pack my bags and go back to Lishui
You'd better go back now
You'd better go back now
It's so late. Who is it?
Gabi na kasi. Sino ito?
He came to congratulate me and said I could win the game today It’s already amazing
Dumating siya para batiin ako at sinabing kaya kong manalo sa laro ngayon It’s already amazing
Tetsuo
Tetsuo
How is it
Paano ba naman
Would you like grilled pork belly with soju?
Would you like grilled pork belly with soju?
Hello Dingchen
Hello Dingchen
why did you come
bakit ka dumating
You're here to celebrate your mom's boyfriend.
You're here to celebrate your mom's boyfriend.
Then you should drink it with your mother Why come here to celebrate?
Then you should drink it with your mother Why come here to celebrate?
Are you unhappy that my mother has a boyfriend?
Are you unhappy that my mother has a boyfriend?
No
Hindi
It's not like you don't know her Can't you help her celebrate?
Hindi naman sa hindi mo siya kilala Hindi mo ba siya matutulungang magdiwang?
Yes, of course I can help her celebrate
Oo, siyempre matutulungan ko siyang mag-celebrate
I just don't know Is this something I can help her celebrate?
Ewan ko lang Ito ba ay isang bagay na maaari kong tulungan siyang ipagdiwang?
Sincere congratulations to your mother Tetsuo
Taos pusong pagbati sa iyong ina na si Tetsuo
Tetsuo, you are so handsome
Tetsuo, ang gwapo mo
How many men in the world would congratulate their mother on her remarriage?
Ilang lalaki sa mundo ang babatiin ang kanilang ina sa kanyang muling pagpapakasal?
Tetsuo
Tetsuo
i wrote a song
nagsulat ako ng kanta
Do you want to listen to it?
Gusto mo bang pakinggan ito?
good
mabuti
"Things of the past"
"Mga bagay ng nakaraan"
"Even if I try hard to remember, I will turn around."
"Kahit pilit kong alalahanin, babalik ako."
"There will still be sad eyes"
"Magkakaroon pa rin ng malungkot na mata"
What a fool
Anong tanga
"Sader than separation"
"Mas malungkot kaysa sa paghihiwalay"
"The words wish me happiness"
"Ang mga salita ay naghahangad sa akin ng kaligayahan"
"Like stars shining in the night sky"
"Tulad ng mga bituin na nagniningning sa kalangitan sa gabi"
"On your pupils"
"Sa iyong mga mag-aaral"
The more I listen to this song, the more it sounds like it
The more I listen to this song, the more na parang ito
Singing about my state of mind
Kumakanta tungkol sa estado ng isip ko
Really?
talaga?
"Tears flow emptyly"
"Walang laman ang luha"
Those stinky dogs
Yung mga mabahong aso
What happened to them
Anong nangyari sa kanila
Brother, leave it to me to solve it
Kuya, ipaubaya mo sa akin ang paglutas nito
As for fighting studies
Tulad ng para sa pakikipaglaban sa pag-aaral
It's your responsibility to stop him
Responsibilidad mong pigilan siya
Never fail
Huwag kailanman mabigo
If Douxue comes to help big brother Things are going to get tricky
Kung dumating si Douxue para tulungan si kuya Magiging mahirap ang mga bagay
What's wrong
anong mali
who are you
sino ka
Wait
Teka
Big brother…
Kuya…
What's wrong? What's wrong?
anong mali? anong mali?
Brother, please take the secret passage and escape.
Kuya, mangyaring kunin ang lihim na daanan at tumakas.
these bastards
mga bastos na ito
where has he gone
saan siya nagpunta
Who?
sino?
You are here
Nandito ka
who are you
sino ka
It's Yongpil
Si Yongpil pala
You came just in time
Dumating ka sa tamang oras
Sure enough, you are the only one I can rely on
Sure enough, ikaw lang ang maaasahan ko
They were sent by Douxue, right?
Pinadala sila ni Douxue, tama ba?
I knew he would be like this
Alam kong magiging ganito siya
But Yongpil
Pero Yongpil
how do you know i'm here
paano mo nalaman na nandito ako
That's right. How would I know?
tama yan. Paano ko malalaman?
Yongbi
Yongbi
Although the sneak attack was successful
Bagama't matagumpay ang sneak attack
But he kept resisting
Ngunit patuloy siyang lumalaban
It's a bit laborious
Medyo matrabaho
Thank you for your hard work
Salamat sa iyong pagsusumikap
Big Brother, your favorite Douxue is here
Kuya, narito ang paborito mong Douxue
"Can I come back to you again?"
"Pwede ba akong bumalik sayo?"
"trembling eyes"
"nanginginig na mata"
"Looks more sad"
"Mukhang mas malungkot"
"My heart is swaying in the desolate sky"
"My heart is swaying in the desolate sky"
"Your name is deeply etched in my heart"
"Your name is deeply etched in my heart"
(Preview of next episode)
(Preview ng susunod na episode)
Prosecutor Choi might have a chance Can you handcuff me?
Prosecutor Choi might have a chance Can you handcuff me?
I said
sabi ko
what was said
what was said
break up
makipaghiwalay
(Wu Wanxu) This is an item confiscated from Lian Guangzhuo's house.
(Wu Wanxu) Ito ay isang bagay na nakumpiska sa bahay ni Lian Guangzhuo.
I found the mastermind
I found the mastermind
who is
sino si
before becoming a family
before becoming a family
There's something I need to let you know first
There's something I need to let you know first
Dingchen
Dingchen
If I don’t join the underworld anymore
If I don’t join the underworld anymore
Do you want to live with me?
Do you want to live with me?
you
ikaw
None of them are human
None of them are human
Go to hell
Pumunta sa impiyerno
This is the hound you killed me price that must be paid
This is the hound you killed me price that must be paid